var questionBank = [
{question:"What country produces the most potatoes?", option1:"China",option2:"United States",option3:"Ireland",option4:"Russia",correctAnswer:"China"},
{question:"In what country would you most likely find chapati on the menu?", option1:"Italy",option2:"Iraq",option3:"India",option4:"Iran",correctAnswer:"India"},
{question:"What is table sugar?", option1:"Fructose",option2:"Glucose",option3:"Otiose",option4:"Sucrose",correctAnswer:"Sucrose"},
{question:"What was the first breakfast cereal ever produced?", option1:"Cornflakes",option2:"Shredded Wheat",option3:"Rice crispies",option4:"Chocolate rice",correctAnswer:"Shredded Wheat"},
{question:"If you were eating mole poblano, you would most likely be in what country?", option1:"Italy",option2:"France",option3:"Mexico",option4:"China",correctAnswer:"Mexico"},
{question:"What is a compote?", option1:"An ice-cream dessert",option2:"Pot-roasted meat",option3:"Fruit juice",option4:"Chunks of fruit in sugar syrup",correctAnswer:"Chunks of fruit in sugar syrup"},
{question:"Peanuts are used in the manufacture of?", option1:"Sleeping pills",option2:"Dynamite",option3:"Tissues",option4:"Toilet roll",correctAnswer:"Dynamite"},
{question:"Apple pie is the official state pie of which state since 1999?", option1:"Alaska",option2:"Virginia",option3:"Vermont",option4:"Montana",correctAnswer:"Vermont"},
{question:"What is hummus made from?", option1:"Tofu",option2:"Chick peas",option3:"Rice",option4:"Corn",correctAnswer:"Chick peas"},
{question:"Something cooked al dente is?", option1:"Firm to the bite",option2:"Soft and spongy",option3:"Raw",option4:"Overcooked",correctAnswer:"Firm to the bite"}

]